YI-PIN HSU

Student

Proactive, worked in drink shop for one and half years, studied in Ming Chuan University International College Applied Computing.

In senior project I have worked as a project manager lead my team member to get first prize in APP invention competition. Furthermore, I have been a class leader for my whole university life.

I have strong learning ability in programming and guitar, during sophomore I started to learn guitar by myself and I approach fingerstyle level which the highest level in guitar in one year.



Email: victorhsu0203@gmail.com

Address: No. 48, Ln. 312, Jianguo Rd., Taoyuan Dist., Taoyuan City 330, Taiwan (R.O.C.)

Phone: (+886)908525057 **Date of birth:** 02-03-1999 **Nationality:** Taiwan

Experience

| July 2019 - January 2021 | Cashier |
|--------------------------|---------|
|--------------------------|---------|

Uni-micron (欣興電子) Taiwan, Taoyuan, Guishan

February 2021 - Present Tutor

Taoyuan cram school Taiwan, Taoyuan, Taoyuan

Excel

Power Point

Help elementary school student to finish their assignment then teach them math

and chinese.

Education

| June 2017 - June 2021 | Appl | lied | Computing | 2 |
|-----------------------|------|------|-----------|---|
| | | | | |

Ming Chuan University International College Taiwan, Taoyuan, Guishan

Languages

Skills

English

HTML CSS JS

Advanced. TOEIC (770)

JS English-Typing Word (55word/hr)

Achievements

APP invention competition first prize

Be Project manager in senior project